export const jsQuizz = {
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        choices: [
          "Virtual DOM",
          "Original DOM",
          "Both A and B",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Virtual DOM",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is not an operating system?",
        choices: [
          "Windows",
          "Linux",
          "Oracle",
          "DOS",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "User Interface framework",
      },
      {
        question:
          " What is the decimal equivalent of the binary number 10111?",
        choices: ["21", "39", "42", "23"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "23",
      },
      {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        choices: ["Python", "Java", "C#", "JavaScript"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
      },
      {
        question: "A process is a?",
        choices: [
          "single thread of execution",
           "program in the execution",
           "program in the memory",
           "task"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "program in the execution",
      },
      {
        question: "If you want to connect to your own computer through the Internet from another location, you can use ?",
        choices: ["FTP ", "e-mail ", "instant message #", "JavaScript"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
      },
      {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        choices: ["e-mail", "Java", "C#", "JavaScript"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
      },
      {
        question: "In which language is React.js written?",
        choices: ["Python", "Java", "C#", "JavaScript"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "JavaScript",
      },
      {
        question: "Codec refers to ?",
        choices: ["Coder-decoder ", "Co-declaration ", "Command declaration", "Command decoding "],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Coder-decoder",
      },
      {
        question: "The synchronous modems are more costly than the asynchronous modems because ?",
        choices: ["They produce large volume of data ", 
          "They contain clock recovery circuits ", 
          "They transmit the data with stop and start bits.",
           "They operate with a larger bandwidth "
          ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "they contain clock recovery circuits",
      },
    ],
  };

  export const resultInitalState={
    score:0,
    correctAnswers:0,
    wrongAnswers:0
  };
